

## **CHARLOTTE**TORDEUR

- +32 (0) 473/24.78.65
- charlottetordeur@gmail.com
- @chammalloww
- www.charlottetordeur.be
- 🚺 🛮 5 Rue des perdrix, Etterbeek



- FRENCH
- ITALIAN
- ENGLISH
- O DUTCH



- PROJECT MANAGEMENT
- WRITING
- O CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP O O O
- O HTML5 & CSS3



## **ABOUT ME**

Hey everyone! I'm Charlotte, I'm 27 years old and I live In Brussels. I'm a jack of all creative trades and I'm fascinated by the cultural communication, the project management, the customer relationship and the entrepreneurship in Brussels.

You can find here the essential of my academic career and my professional career.

If my profile interests you, do not hesitate to contact me!

You can also visit my website www.charlottetordeur.be



## **EDUCATION**

- O CPAB de Bruxelles | NOVEMBER 2013 APRIL 2014 Dutch classes three days a week.
- ▼ Tamwood International College MAY 2013 SEPTEMBER 2013 English Certificate: English classes at Tamwood College, Vancouver, Canada.
- Université libre de Bruxelles SEPTEMBER 2010 JUNE 2012
  Master's degree, Cultural management: Various internships and marketing classes, marketing communication, management control, human ressources management, accouting and and copyright laws.
- Facultés universitaires Saint-Louis SEPTEMBER 2006 JUNE 2010
  Bachelor's degree, French language and literary, : Linguistics classes, French literary, medieval history, art history, philosophy, Italian culture and language.



## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES**

Impulse.brussels, department information JUNE 2015 - NOW & network,1819

**Advisor:** My mission is to inform, to advice and to give direction to the (future) entrepreneurs in order to support the development of the entrepreneurship in Brussels.

- Moulinsart, Musée Hergé JUNE 2014 MAY 2015
  Sales manager: at Musée Hergé's Shop.
- Institut Saint-Boniface Parnasse | MARCH 2014 APRIL 2014
  French teacher: Replacement contract.
- **⊙** Ecole Montgomery | FEBRUARY 2014 FEBRUARY 2014 French teacher: Replacement contract.
- Studios Hergé | SEPTEMBER 2012 OCTOBER 2012 NOVEMBER 2011 MARCH 2012 Internship: I developped different kinds of educational projects.